A Guide to the Press Office Records of Virginia Governor George F. Allen, 1993-1998
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Press Office Records of Virginia Governor George F. Allen, 1993-1998
The Library of Virginia
35430, 35715, 35716, 35746, 35863, 43396
36.75 cubic feet
Virginia. Governor (1994-1998: Allen)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 35430 donated by Melissa Herring, Governor's Office, Press Office, Richmond, Virginia, 4 June 1997.
Accessions 35715, 35716, and 35746 transferred by Georgia Root, Assistant Secretary of the Commonwealth, Richmond, Virginia, 13 February 1998.
Accession 35863 transferred by Georgia Root, Assistant Secretary of the Commonwealth, Richmond, Virginia, 19 June 1998.
Accession 43396 transferred by Pierre Courtois, Photographer, Library of Virginia, Richmond, Virginia, 5 April 2007.
Biographical Information
George Felix Allen was born March 8, 1952 in Whittier, California to famed NFL football coach George H. Allen and his wife Henrietta (Lumbroso) Allen. He graduated from the University of Virginia in 1971 and the University of Virginia School of Law in 1977. Allen served in the Virginia House of Delegates from 1982-1991 and served a short term in the U.S. House of Delegates in the early 1990s. In November 1993, Allen beat Attorney General Mary Sue Terry to become Governor. Governor Allen served until January 1998 and was succeeded by Governor James S. Gilmore. Governor Allen has been married to Susan (Brown) Allen since 1986 and they have three children, Forrest, Tyler, and Brooke. The family resides in Mount Vernon, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Contains news summaries, photographs, press releases, publications, proclamations and certificates of recognition, speeches, and other files related to the activities of Governor George F. Allen's Press Office. The Press Office was responsible for keeping the media and the general public informed of Governor Allen's appearances, speech writing, issuing proclamations, and maintaining the Governor's photograph collection. The Press Office also collected information related to the Governor, such as newspaper clippings and magazine articles.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. News Summaries
Series II. Photographs
Series III. Press Releases and Publications
Series IV. Proclamations and Certificates of Recognition
Series V. Publications
Series VI. Speeches
Series VII. Miscellaneous Press Office Files
Contents List
- Series I. News Summaries, 1994-1998., Extent: 25 cubic feet. (Box 1-25)
  (Accession 35715). Contains packets of news clippings related to Governor Allen and his administration. In many cases, the clippings are indexed according to subject matter. These packets were compiled by the Press Office. Also included are packets of news clippings compiled by the Virginia Press Service (VPS Clips) that are also indexed by subject. VPS Clips are found at the end of each month. Researchers should note that overlap may or may not exist between the two sets of clippings.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1994.
    - January 18-19. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - January 20-21. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - January 24-25. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - January 26-27. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - January 28-31. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - February 1-2. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - February 3-4. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - February 7. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - February 8. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - February 10. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - February 12. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - February 13. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - February 14. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - February 15. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - February 16. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - February 17. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - February 18. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - February 19-20. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - February 21-22. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - February 23. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - February 24. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - February 25. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - February 26-28. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - March 1-2. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - March 3-4. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - March 5-6. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - March 7-8. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - March 9. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - March 10. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - March 11. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - VPS Clips, January-March. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - March 12. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - March 14. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - March 15. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - March 16-17. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - March 18-21. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - March 22-23. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - March 24-25. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - March 28-29. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - March 30-31. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - VPS Clips, March 20-27. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - VPS Clips, March. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - April 1-4. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - April 5-6. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - April 7-8. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - April 9-11. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - April 12-13. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - April 14-15. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - April 16-18. (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - April 19. (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - April 20-21. (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - April 22-23. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - April 25-26. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - April 27-28. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - April 29-30. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - VPS Clips, April. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - May 2-3. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - May 4-5. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - May 6-9. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - VPS Clips, May. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips, May. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - VPS Clips, May 31. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - June 1-2. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - June 3. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - June 4-5. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - June 6-7. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - June 8-9. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - June 10-12. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - June 13-14. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - June 15-16. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - June 17-19. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - June 20-21. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - June 22-24. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - June 25-27. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - June 28-30. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - News Clips, April-June. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - News Clips, June. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - News Clips, June-July. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - VPS Clips, June-July. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - July 1-2. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - July 5-6. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - July 7. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - July 8-11. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - July 12. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - July 13. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - July 14-15. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - July 18. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - July 19. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - July 20. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - July 21. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - July 22-26. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - July 26-27. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - July 28-29. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Press Clips (Lost), July. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - July 30-August 2. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - August 3-4. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - August 5. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - August 6-8. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - August 9-11. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - August 12-15. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - August 16-18. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - August 19. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - August 20-23. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - August 24-25. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - August 26-29. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - August 30-31. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - News Clips, August. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - VPS Clips, July-August. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - September 1-2. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - September 6-7. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - September 8-9. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - September 10-13. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - September 14-15. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - September 16-19. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - September 20-21. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - September 22-23. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - September 24-26. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - September 27-28. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - September 29-30. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - News Clips, September. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - VPS Clips, September-October. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - October 1-4. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - October 5-6. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - October 7-11. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - October 12. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - October 13-14. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - October 16-19. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - October 20-21. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - October 22-24. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - October 25-26. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - October 27-28. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Ocotber 29-31. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - News Clips, October. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - VPS Clips, September-October. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - November 1-2. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - November 3-4. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - November 5-8. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - November 9-10. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - November 11-14. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - November 15-17. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - November 18-21. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - November 22-28. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - November 29-30. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - News Clips, November. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - VPS Clips, October-November. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - December 1-2. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - December 3-6. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - December 8-10. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - December 11-13. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - December 14-16. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - December 16-20. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - December 21-23. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - December 27-28. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - December 29-30. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - News Clips, December. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - News Clips, December. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips, December. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - VPS Clips, December. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1995.
    - January 3. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - January 4-6. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - January 7-8. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - January 9-10. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - January 11. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - January 12-13. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - January 14-16. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - January 17. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - January 18-19. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - January 20-21. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - January 22-24. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - January 25. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - January 26-27. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - January 28-29. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - January 30-31. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - News Clips, January. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - VPS Clips (Parts II-III), January. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - VPS Clips (Part IV), January. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - VPS Clips (Part V), January. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - VPS Clips (Parts VI-VII), January. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips (Part VIII), January. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - February 1. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - February 2-3. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - February 4-5. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - February 6-7. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - February 8-9. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - February 10-11. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - February 13-14. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - February 15-16. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - February 17-19. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - February 20-21. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - February 22-23. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - February 24-26. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - February 27-28. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - VPS Clips, January-February. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - March 1-3. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - March 4-6. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - March 7-9. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - March 10-13. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - March 14-16. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - March 17-20. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - March 21-24. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - March 25-28. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - March 29-31. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), March. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips (Part III), March. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - VPS Clips (Part VI-VII), March. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - April 1-4. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - April 5-7. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - April 8-10. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - April 11-12. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - April 13-14. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - April 17-19. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - April 20-22. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - April 23-25. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - April 26-30. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), April. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - VPS Clips (Parts III-IV), April. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - May 1-3. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - May 4-6. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - May 7-10. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - May 11-15. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - May 16-17. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - May 18-20. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - May 21-24. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - May 25-26. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - May 27-31. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - VPS Clips, April-May. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - VPS Clips (Parts II-III), May. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - June 1-3. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - June 4-7. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - June 8-9. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - June 12. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - June 13-15. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - June 16-18. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - June 19-22. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - June 23-27. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - June 28-30. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), June. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - July 1-6. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - July 7-11. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - July 12-15. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - July 16-19. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - July 20-23. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - July 24-26. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - July 27-28. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - July 29-31. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Listening Tour, July 10-30. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), July. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - VPS Clips (Parts III-IV), July. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - August 1-4. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - August 5-7. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - August 8-10. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - August 11-14. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - August 15-16. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - August 17-20. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - August 21-23. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - August 24-25. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - August 26-28. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - August 29-31. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), August. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - September 1-4. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - September 5-7. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - September 8-11. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - September 12-13. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - September 14-15. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - September 16-17. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - September 19-20. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - September 21-22. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - September 23-25. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - September 26-28. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - September 29-30. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-III), September. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - VPS Clips (Part IV), September. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - October 1-3. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ocotber 4-6. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - October 7-10. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - October 11-12. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - October 13-16. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - October 17. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - October 18-19. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - October 20-22. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - October 23-24. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - October 25-26. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - October 27-29. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - October 30-31. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), October. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - VPS Clips (Parts III-IV), October. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - November 1-2. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - November 3. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - November 4-5. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - November 6. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - November 7. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - November 8. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - November 9. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - November 10-13. (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - November 14-15. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - November 16. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - November 17. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - November 18-20. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - November 21-22. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - November 23-28. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - November 29-30. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - VPS Clips (Parts II and IV), November. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - VPS Clips (Parts V and VI), November. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - VPS Clips, November. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips November. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - December 1-2. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - December 4-5. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - December 6-7. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - December 8-10. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - December 11-13. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - December 14. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - December 15-16. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - December 17-19. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - December 20-22. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - December 23-31. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I and II), December. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - VPS Clips (Parts III and IV), December. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1996.
    - January 1. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - January 2-6. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - January 9-11. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - January 12-14. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - January 15-17. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - January 18-20. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - January 21-23. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - January 24-26. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - January 27-29. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - January 30-31. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-II), January. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - VPS Clips (Parts III-IV), January. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - February 1-3. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - February 4-6. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - February 7. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - February 8-10. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - February 11-12. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - February 13. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - February 14. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - February 15. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - February 16-18. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - February 19-20. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - February 21. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - February 22-23. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - February 24-26. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - February 27. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - February 28-29. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-IV), February. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - March 1-3. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - March 4-5. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - March 6-7. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - March 8-9. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - March 10-11. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - March 12. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - March 13-14. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - March 15-17. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - March 18-19. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - March 20-21. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - March 22-24. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - March 25-26. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - March 27. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - March 28-29. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - March 30-31. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-IV), March. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - April 1-3. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - April 4. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - April 5. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - April 6-9. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - April 10-12. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - April 14-15. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - April 16-17. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - April 18-19. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - April 20-22. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - April 23-25. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - April 26-27. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - April 28-30. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - VPS Clips (Part I), April. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - May 1-2. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - May 3-5. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - May 6-8. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - May 9. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - May 10. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - May 11-13. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - May 14-16. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - May 17-19. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - May 20-22. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - May 23-26. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - May 27-28. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - May 29-31. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - VPS Clips (Parts I-III), May. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - June 1-3. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - June 4-5. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - June 6-7. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - June 8-10. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - June 11-12. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - June 13-15. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - June 16-18. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - June 19-21. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - June 22-25. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - June 26-27. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - June 28-30. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - July 1-3. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - July 4-7. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - July 8-10. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - July 11-12. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - July 13-15. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - July 16-18. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - July 19-22. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - July 23-24. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - July 25-28. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - July 29-31. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - VPS Clips (Part I), July. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - August 1-3. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - August 4-6. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - August 7-9. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - August 10-13. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - August 14-15. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - August 16-18. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - August 19-21. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - August 22-23. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - August 24-27. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - August 28-31. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - VPS Clips (Part I), August. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - September 1-4. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - September 5-6. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - September 7-9. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - September 10-12. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - September 13-15. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - September 16-18. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - August 19-21. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - September 22-24. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - September 25-27. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - September 28-30. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - VPS Clips (Part I), September. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - October 1-4. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - October 5-8. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - October 9-10. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - October 11-13. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - October 14-16. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - October 17-19. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - October 20-22. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - October 23-25. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - October 26-28. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - October 29-31. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - November 1-4. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - November 5-6. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - November 7-10. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - November 11-13. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - November 14-17. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - November 18-20. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - November 21-22. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - November 23-26. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - November 27-30. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - December 1-3. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - December 4-5. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - December 6-8. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - December 9-11. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - December 12-15. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - December 16-18. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - December 19-22. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - December 23-24. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - December 26-27. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - December 28-31. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - VPS Clips, December. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - VPS Clips, December. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 1997.
    - January 1-3. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - January 4-6. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - January 7-9. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - January 10-11. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - January 12-13. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - January 14-16. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - January 17-19. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - January 21-22. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - January 23. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - January 24-26. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - January 27. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Janaury 28-29. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - January 30-31. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - February 1-2. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - February 3-4. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - February 5. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - February 7. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - February 8-10. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - February 11-12. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - February 13-15. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - February 16-18. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - February 19. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - February 20-21. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - February 22-24. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - February 25-26. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - February 27-28. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - VPS Clips, February. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - VPS Clips, February. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - VPS Clips, February. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - March 1-3. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - March 4-5. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - March 6. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - March 7-9. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - March 10-12. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - March 13-14. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - March 15-17. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - March 18. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - March 22-24. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - March 25-26. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - March 27-28. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - March 29-31. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips, March. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - VPS Clips, March. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - VPS Clips, March. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - VPS Clips, March. (Box 20, Folder 12)